the good news is it has SiC upstream
bell
look at that sick upstream bandwidth you
know what up welcome welcome
I've kept it with me I've kept it with
me since Osaka so yeah we got sick
upload bandwidth I'm sick
it still works
my own normal time now I feel like I'm
on the same time I was before but yes
where were we not there by the
transistor section - yes we wrote this
flash last time you can dump the things
I texted my mom was sitting out man she
text me back she said looks industrial
it's hella cheap gross I'm in a
five-star hotel it's cheap you know I
love cheap no I'm not Norway of non
Sweden no you guys are there that's cool
yeah no it's kind of industrial man take
a quick look outside just show you
outside I'll be real impressed or anyone
can guess the city
let's Thanksgiving at home no I'm not
Philadelphia don't think I wanna chat
yeah so what we were gonna try to do is
we downloaded the Xilinx tools did I own
zip them anywhere yeah I wanted to try
to well they're doing some interesting
stuff there's this new hardware
description language that people are
using it synthesizes things from Python
so let's see what we can do
there's also this interesting thing
called Noah which can do which can run
Linux apps on a Mac no of course yeah
you go back when Ubuntu with Mac OS X so
maybe we could try to install this
I have no let's do this it seems cool
see I don't think I don't want anything
too sketchy yeah so it's this okay I
unzipped it oh you probably gonna want
to zoom in more I get my comments up my
phone
it's been a while yo don't dissing jazzy
you're lucky your subscriber now we're
gonna do that shit anymore you know we
get all a little piece of stuff
alright so unsupported platform Darwin
what are we gonna do about this so
design links tools in a docker
yeah this broke did it
I don't know if no is any good but we're
trying to install it so we're gonna see
what happens I don't think it's good but
I'm interested what else was I looking
at I was looking also I really started
my team looks pretty deep
could I use some download manager click
or get well gets a download manager I
guess it can resume yeah no I know you
can't see I know where you can't see
don't worry I'll try to keep things away
from there to launch it just was da cap
to make sure it has no network access
I don't know what doc app is talk about
it here
yeah no I'm kidding I'm kidding about
the dissing of New Jersey Saturday but
it's better than with a lot of the rest
of America like California which is on
fire fuckers
that's right let's San Francisco burn no
it's a real tragedy a lot of people dive
in wildfire campfire ridiculous shit
let's put me up there I have with that
how's that sound good guys gonna see the
bottom here all right
[Music]
two things know it works
yeah I wish I can fly call duty like mr.
Kim comm they'd be pretty awesome I'm
not that awesome okay so how do I make a
doll cap I don't even know
did this priority do it all this bro is
genius did you do it I think he did it
I'll say included as island shell script
which allows installation of impact
inside his daughter oh what a noob he
would get sit into the thing did he run
like a surfer or something why does he
would get it okay so I think he wants me
to copy all those files just on gir day
definite all so much megabytes Wow take
so long yeah I know I know I know it
sucks
I don't know that normally this this
place has pretty good bandwidth hey I
don't wanna down was update this
bullshit I don't care
Noah is still under development no I
have no name until I run like Noah and
then I run exhale cat scan or you go up
that install always have to suit over
that don't I whatever what
I'm on you I'm on you and I know it's
garbage see if they're gonna work error
response from David no bathed it basic
auth credentials great
oh okay that build it
on eye candy route
thank you for hosting me but what I
really appreciate is you know I love
when people subscribe
I can't even shelf for subscribers
anymore I think that's played out my
best played out
no more shelling we're just here to kind
of chill on computer you know it's just
chilling on computer die maybe we'll
rant about politics guys no not to turn
freespace what see you have that follow
director I understand couldn't determine
free space stop via pass no such watch
don't have a fucking Google account you
see that shit you think I'm in Google
bought Google do you package - I was
that users so is that now in my main var
- no that's a different but it is users
stays the same that's so weird
home has users
well that's after getting in the docker
container right now okay I'm kind of
over Noah know what kind of sucks docker
is kind of good we love docker was Jesus
a copy of some bullshit thank you for
subscribing thank you with thank you for
subscribing
John Razer I love him people subscribe
how much time I spent the day doing this
and spent any time doing this I'm told
but now I've been thinking about the
future Bros I've been thinking about my
friend we're always telling us like like
Paris gathering of the artists forgot
what it was called yeah yeah they had
like Paris salons you know back in the
day but today if you had a salon they
would like you know SEO promote the shit
out of it come to our salon conference
extravaganza where you can speak about
the value of collaboration and what the
fuck is collaboration oh we're really in
the 21st century we really need a more
collaborative workplace what does that
mean like people used to not collaborate
and now they collaborate I don't even
know yeah see I knew oh my god okay it
does look good oh I see what it wants
okay
[Music]
you don't do that um hang on
so Yap jetted all those things I don't
have those files
no not muting the keyboard subscribe
don't think about listening to the
keyboard is most of the reason you
listen to my twitch script you can just
do that with ATAR okay well this guy
clearly didn't know how to do docker
shares directory
target term equals x time root
to install
[Music]
so weird why does it would get can't
seed a root in stone yeah yeah yeah get
rid of that okay
let's try that
Oh interesting
is it like a 2gig limit or some shit
it's not putting those in da core it
doesn't have to do that I don't think um
add files yeah I don't wanna do that
okay work I think take a long time I
don't have trouble I just share a folder
between container
work dear
booter docker no I've seen this done no
I have another doctor where I do this
whenever it's almost done it's well he
sent the build context to the dock or
daemon by now
who loves docker I love talker
[Music]
yeah - V how can I do this in dockerfile
that's what I want I want to do in Dhaka
fuck my way to the chef
don't few things I'm getting kind of
annoyed it you know what we're gonna fix
this now was it just gonna piss me off
start my team up there put the tar balls
right there fine you know what
sometimes it's just easier to make
things happy than to try to do things in
that way my bill here we go
fail connection refused why do not run
the stupid Python web server
[Music]
or does it not forward the port or
something may be fine I found I see that
file oh it doesn't have lint oh okay
fine
see so much subtlety was in the
dockerfile what do you mean connection
refused how I different mrs. Pawley
commands I misspell stuff constantly I
just keep doing it
playing container ports to the host but
I want to buy no I want with the other
way around
why is connection refused right over
here and I start the Python server cello
connection I've used okay well I guess
local house doesn't mean local host
I think that's the other way around
exposing ports
publish all expose forth to the whole
surface range of ports now I want to do
the opposite of expose you know I'm
saying
locker access post networks
I mean I can't I get why you would get
guys playing with Zula hearing this
docker file cool docker file it exposes
just just press it doesn't crash that's
a run stupid you know don't do that
accessing hosts from a docker container
as far as a little broken
host are darker that in turn is that
mark locals they do that does that work
pretty funny
how cool works well I was gonna take
five minutes when I was slow yes thank
you dr. dot 4 dot Mad Max don't have a
scale what you talk about
oh my god it's take forever it there's
gotta be a faster way to do this poor
design sure dad's file so how can I just
mount dollar amount
[Music]
this is better
vol I'm not waiting for that it took
over
des you know what that does a little
thing I playing with does us okay so I
lied I was playing with computers a
little bit I blow it up as a woman you
know I was kind of uh my feelings for
urban and I was like why would I have a
Herbet when I get Eva's ooh lip work der
this no it's all sorts of global things
oh this is too complicated what I want
oh there's a docker compose your volumes
this when I add a volume to a docker
file volume
odds that's gonna work come on over
can access time so thank you thank you
for subscribing thank you I'm so happy
with people subscribe that should work
right
I don't dockerfile is really so poorly
documented
[Music]
Darrin's onyx installer cannot open no
such file or directory um I've made
enough to make the directory first
volume
okay maybe just these coals don't work
wait we carry it all the way bullshit
bullshit
that looks like it took a long time it's
probably pretty good what'd she make
sense why just a one container Linux go
starting to dinner
yes so work starting container product
self-help FD no such file or directory
is this one work ok that's a different
problem yeah that's fine but the volume
breaks
so I'm new to docker guys posin was good
at docker copies Island installer times
but I don't want to copy maybe copy
failed oh because it's not darker
context ah what but that's an absolute
path so there's I've seen this before
it's like what's allowed to be volumes
users is fine okay let's check I just
put the CTF had this stuff yeah second I
know that's that coming cold blow
there's one docker compose this I
haven't seen a docker file before yeah
they said they have copies there but no
I'm gonna copy I don't want to copy I
want volume the problem is the file is
very large
you know in retrospect we just get away
to the five hits for the word gap the
volumes are mounted when running the
container
you can mount with Daddy parameter Oh
cuz it's running the container doctor
run with mounted volume another way to
do this yeah yeah and no I know what
you're talking about okay so let's try
that I'm not doctor running it I'm dr.
bill can I do it in docker build as well
any chance that's going to work save -
Dee
did this ever happen in
what
so confusing
not possible this is garbage who
invented this bullshit wait so you're
telling me I can't mount a volume during
docker build all right who wants to wait
while the we get happens I guess that
really was the best way to do it
I guess broski was smarter than we
thought I'm offended okay with 24
minutes while the we got happens whoo
you can mount with D parameter on docker
run yeah it's not you can't do in a
darker build you can only do it on
docker you already said that so just get
the way what should we do only way geez
what should we do yo no I don't know if
these hotel people know what streaming
is but they probably just think I'm
crazy and talking to myself you know
we want to rant about well sure your
rant about I want hi so I'm here in
let's just call it rapidly
industrializing nation and I'm hoping
that somewhere in the world there's a
renaissance you know somewhere in the
world people are thinking new thoughts
and it isn't just the same rehashed shit
guys the internet do you know why the
stream can't get popular because the
Internet is overrun with shit and the
second anything gets popular its overrun
with shit and the only things that can
thrive in such an environment is gucci
gang and we're gonna watch gucci gang
because gucci gang this is a great song
and it's all that can try in today's
internet environment so if you like
gucci getting for i have no idea i don't
read anything about stupid ass politics
anymore
[Music]
my beloved in Spokane oh yeah today's
world guys this is all take some
percocet I guess on airplane
WestJet and he acts like you didn't yet
if it kick him off you don't know what
it's about it's not about anything
it's not about we're just here to have a
good time in program we're not trying to
do anything which is chilling well I
don't know muscles am but guys this is
all I can exist in today's world
[Music]
because you can't good together good
again good you gay wow that's all we get
no we're not in Taiwan we're in let's
say rapidly industrializing nation
number seven
Plateau a card this is a real thing like
I've never heard of this yep this is
like what we get is it the same die lit
sound like just song I know listen to
play were quite cool guys here we go
[Music]
I'm gonna collect which copyrights
gucchi gang was at least table all's me
um why are we in rapidly industrializing
nation number seven because
Oh hiding in his socks not my music is
my music is is even more shit than this
Oh
Oh after all that we couldn't even
execute the thing
good you can couch again Gucci gang
couch again
oh well no shit
well how do I get tired of strip off we
have to wait for - we'll get again
[Music]
just do it here no no no it's rapidly
industrializing nation number seven it's
a nice place hotel in the place in the
city I'm sure there's a nicer hotels if
you go to the other cities as well very
affordable goochy goochy goochy getting
good children oh he's probably hiding
from the cops wow that makes sense
hiding in his socks that doesn't make
sense we're gonna send the the six
gigabyte build context to the darker
daemon but actually it's faster than we
get maybe one of those countries rapidly
industrializing nation number seven no
this is Ike you think I'd be talking
about anything North Korea I'd be like
horrified like I've been horrified at
the guy like you know North Korea's got
a lot of people they probably got some
people I mean let's go out people play
North Korea is probably got some people
outside my hotel room you know I don't
think they got people outside my hotel
room here I don't think it's that kind
of place and they're pretty chill as
long as you don't like bring drugs into
the country
will pump you can't you can't bring your
leave here no way in here is legal light
just like just like you know rapidly
industrializing nations one through six
drugs are highly illegal here they
execute a few people makes a good point
people are afraid no one brings drugs
into the country people do take crazy no
no no I'm not in war-torn nation number
three whoa
no bra appreciate
it's now so Singapore I don't think I'd
call Singapore rapidly industrializing
nation number seven I think I would call
Singapore a member of the drinkable
water club here we have bottled water
because the water is not really
drinkable huge my hard drive what I much
know number seven all right it's not
like Japan and Singapore where you can
drink the water
the Singapore part of Malaysia no
separate country in fact Singapore
wanted to be a part of Malaysia in the
60s but if I recall correctly Malaysia
said no I believe I believe don't get me
wrong on this but it was good Singapore
at race riots Malaysia was like fuck
this yet we don't want you as part of
our nice country you think things are
happening in Scandinavia maybe oh yeah
here we go
all this is good all things are
happening oh yeah Gucci can couch again
Gucci Gucci gang
oh but see I don't want this I don't
want this because now these things are
gonna be too large or I have like docker
clean up all this bullshit well dog or
kill dog or kill star that's not gonna
work okay last time last time we do this
well now we know it works or just we're
gonna do the we get again
because if you don't do the look at if
you don't do the would get it's gonna
leave a huge image lying around in the
context but we need to pass the flag
guitar
okay we're all just here chilling you
know and on any rush
[Music]
yeah that's stripped components equals
one that's it we want you to figure out
how to clean up old docker containers
I don't know why these are running all
right miss Beldon carnal
I've been rapidly industrialized nation
number seven maybe I will take a train
and I will end up and rapidly
industrializing nation number six are
you doing potable like yeah that's cool
you can drink the water in Taiwan our
country is no longer rapidly
industrializing can you drink the water
in Taiwan wait really
oh okay figure out how many docker lists
all containers it's just the ones that's
up how do I list all docker yes - hey oh
yeah look at these
we're gonna kill that and I'm gonna RM
all my Dockers
oh yeah look at all that bullshit image
is being used
well right
Thank You Colonel ice for subscribing
thank you the major so happy to have you
all subscribers wait you want to know
about CTF so I'll see what's coming up
the generic which again that you can get
together
you know looking at this before that's
worth play
okay Qualls is next January I don't know
any of these CTFs it's long before my
time
second finals is the day before
Christmas
oh docker system crew oh cool thank you
for the useful docker information we're
just learning how to use docker casually
docker boom doctor system for wow I've
have any gigabyte stuff
we're in a space we'll do that to thank
you Alex says look cool
it is mac OS mojave that is true how we
do everything in mac OS I so let's just
figure out how this xilinx ISE alright
so bro
sorry for saying using we get was stupid
who can actually turned out to be the
best solution which is sad
which is sad has said yeah final image
has about 30 gigabytes or so much
gigabytes
but any NYSEG Cylons just provided an
image we're also gonna figure out why
Xilinx is six gigabytes once we start
making things with it you know working
my benching strength I'm gonna do some
push-ups do some push-ups
let's do push-ups let's do push-ups bras
keep down let's do ten push-ups very
stupid
most a tempest of sunlight good job good
job good you can't get rich again no the
malls still open for another hour
like in all rapidly industrializing
nations they have malls that will just
blow your mind the size of these malls
people in these malls the cleanliness of
these moms as contrast to the rest of
their nation the malls are beautiful
oh shit really didn't work that's
nothing right how was that mother put it
up before xvf and I have to weigh
together that's so stupid
oh shit all right
oh they put it after
yeah I mean no other malls you're
unbelievable
oh you wanted to say goochie goochie
goochie goochie gang
I got bitch loves cocaine
Mylene cost more than your rent but your
mom lives in a tent range oh yeah
arraigned around
I'm across the street from a mall we
really impressed by figure out where
this is spent I saw a new chat mob
there's loud dude cocaine yeah
yo monster genius never mind I take back
all the things I said about our culture
being in decline
Gucci gang is clearly the pinnacle of
artistic achievements no it's not it's a
rapidly industrializing nation number
seven I was actually cuz they have a
hair condition which I am in I am in the
nicest hotel in this city in rapidly
industrializing nation number seven I'm
okay Internet yeah it's surprisingly
surprisingly when I was when I was in
rapidly industrializing nation number
nine I couldn't really stream because
the internet wasn't good enough but this
is rapidly industrializing asian number
seven and the Internet's a bit better
here you got to give it all of course
China is rapidly industrializing nation
umber one so I'll let you guys in on
that and I'm not in I'm not in China
does that would be on number one once
the country has clean water I think it's
a sanitation is really dead I have less
doubts about him being really dead the
little peep being really dead it will
peep staged his death it did wonders for
his career accent Asian got like shot at
a car dealership thumb shed in China
number one yeah that's true
and then maybe maybe all the countries
that have drinkable tap water that don't
get a name too but I'm not sure what
they are yet it includes places like
Singapore Japan and maybe Taiwan no
Taiwan's a part of China that's right
Taiwan is a part of
I don't know I don't know if tywanza
whatever will make the people happy you
know this is my new politics this isn't
my new politics oh yeah his mother
really yeah come over when you're sober
part two way weaker people never let
that shit out I think but you know his
balls bacon Oh India
no no but here's my new strategy about
all politically controversial stuff if
someone has like an opinion
you just asked them what you think what
should I believe you tell me what I
should believe and I will believe it I
love that it's a great strategy
India India never been to India I have
heard about Delhi Belly a little afraid
to go to India coming I as bands and
talking here I'm know about India I'm
not an idiot
I'm sick but let's just might throw this
also it's not like I'm not like don't go
her toilet which I don't know I know if
I get sick I should go to India before I
talk shit I've been to Italy I've been
to Italy um
true honest opinion of Italy especially
Florence like I felt like I was just
like like Florence was like Disneyland
like it's not this isn't even a city
anymore this is just tourists
I came during July and Florence was just
hordes and hordes of tourists and then
the whole city economy was just built to
the tourists um I'm afraid to go to
Africa for different reasons I'm India I
would go to at most of Africa and
legitimately just too afraid to go to a
bitch let's see what the state governor
Pakistan
I really like steak up yeah I didn't
even I didn't even go Milan I liked
Milan I met a girl in Milan why was I
the you know he has drinkable tap water
it's one of those nations it's a
drinkable tap water nation you know I
like to go in India sometime I don't
know um
okay well I'm not gonna Pakistan anytime
soon but is the problem really terrorism
I'm really not that worried about about
terror there's always like like you know
like Singapore has a travel warning for
terrorism for some reason it doesn't
scare me although actually I really like
this website and um Bo
where they rank all the cities by crime
you guys remember when I was in Osaka
Osaka is like the safest city in the
world except for these cities which
these cities scare me for instance you
know when you want to talk about freedom
you can talk about there's like crime as
an example of like private people
infringing on your liberties and then
there's government infringing on your
liberties in these places I don't know
actually I should do more research
before I say this these places I trust
that as long as that like like Singapore
and Japan I trust that like as long as I
follow their rules everything's fine um
I could probably go to Jakarta in UAE
yeah telling no no no this is low crime
this is low crime telling it's very safe
I'd like to go and that's yeah I've been
hearing about Georgia lately I'm
interested um like I didn't I was I
hmm let's go
um now when I went Italy I saw some guys
with a case
I've never been to Iraq Iran or
Afghanistan I think that they are all
heavily advised against traveling by the
US State Department I am a US citizen
I've heard actually nice things about
Iran if I felt like I was like going
with the right people and for the right
reasons I'd be happy to go to Iran I got
arrested it's a safe country nada no
drugs here don't worry no drugs no drugs
metabolites of my system who said we're
in Malaysia what we're rapidly
industrializing nation number seven
Philippines is rapidly industrializing
nation number eight yeah I probably
can't go to Iran but I've heard
surprisingly good things about Georgia
despite being sandwiched in between like
this rush is the same sort of thing like
I felt I would feel good about going to
Russia if I was going with the right
people I wouldn't just want to go to
Russia by myself or I've heard they just
kill you in Chechnya is that true um yet
no I've heard I've heard surprising the
nice things about George how's the
political situation in Turkey I don't
know about the political situation in
Turkey
there's Snowden the last person I would
want to hang out with in Russia is
Edward Snowden do I want a government
tail for the rest of my life no thanks
Georgia has a weird language they have a
Trump Tower in Georgia Russia yeah but
no I'm interested in uh I'm interested
in Poznan Poland like I've never really
been much to Eastern Europe but uh
really nice things actually Estonia meet
Justin Tollan I've heard rumors that
Finland didn't exist so I can't check
for myself Ovid Germany in Palatine
spent a lot of time going and yeah and
then we have over here the land of
rapidly industrializing nations
I've heard yes oh yeah I kind of maybe
I'll make a stopover in Georgia
is and another thing is how's the
eastern Ukraine is stable or not I mean
the most I know about eastern Ukraine is
when the guy shot that plane down
you love goat ah he was tahi go to Dubai
to ride camels can I just like go to
Dubai would that be chill device down
here isn't it yeah I guess it would be
ya know I might be way less sketched out
like gonna do by then going like Saudi
Arabia
yeah don't xed yeah what's that I don't
know I don't know anything about that
Jacob lies dead hopefully I trust that
it's fine now yeah
all these rapidly industrializing
nations
I do miss the freedom in America in
America America is the only place I've
ever been where I feel like I have like
rights I feel like in all of these
places you know it's it's I'm here as
their guest and I appreciate that I
appreciate that
obviously I'm a traveler in these
countries I appreciate them having me
here and I really will try my best to
follow their rules um but when you like
don't follow their rules like I'd never
want to mess around with that because
it's not like you have rights if you
don't follow the rules in America you
have rights um no I don't feel freedom
in Europe in the same way either
especially with some of like the America
has very strong protections here America
has historically the best protections
again for freedom of speech so I feel
like despite a lot of its shortcomings
America does have freedom I mean there's
countries this places where I guess I
would feel more like personal freedoms
yeah you can go go go go to beliefs like
John McAfee you hire an army yeah he got
you got real personal freedom in a sense
in a in a messed up sort of way
I made the chili Chili's pretty nice
I'd be scared to go to a lot of the rest
of South America now very high crime
curry is beautiful I love Korea there's
been a lot of times in South Korea not
I've been to Greece oh I'm in my
checking Greece out my sister spent a
lot of time that my sister like is a
teacher there I went to Santiago in
Valparaiso
all right it's taking forever no not the
Doubletree I'm not the devil - bro if
you're not American you have very low
rights in America I think that's
probably a lot of the news talking if
you're an illegal immigrant sure but if
you are not an American citizen but you
came to the country legally you have you
have all the rights a meanness a
question it's a question American
society like do do illegal immigrants
are they covered under America's like
Constitution it's unclear but if you
come to America illegally of course of
course you're the same rights the same
rights I do as I said I mean at least
under Constitution you definitely show
politics guys like politics is like oh I
think the government should pay more for
this I think the taxes should be less oh
I think the health care should be free I
think the health care should cost more
money and be run by corporations that's
what politics is a stupid um we're
talking about like rights and
sovereignty is someone more interesting
to me I really think of this politics
all right cool
hmm so we have an image now let's say
silence does work well I think it works
oh I think it works
[Music]
okay Noah was a big disappointment
all right all right no no no politics no
no politics my point was just about
whether you know you have rights in
America and what the debate was over you
could talk about what the debate is over
without picking a side you know what no
no no no the illegal immigrants should
be gunned down Dan okay you get a
timeout don't say that shit all right
all right all right don't say that shit
come on
God exists of I guess that's the rule
that's the rule about political
discussion if you want to say some about
politics is gotta be funny that's I
think that would be a great rule I think
you know we should all have great
discussions no yelling no being angry
just funny - no mind killer that's -
that's true
all right so where are we you guys long
you guys love the diversions yeah here
we go all right my boy Chris is 2600
it's very subjective no no no it's not
that subjective your reer people but
people always like people when they talk
about politics the like like though
they'll say like you know dumb shit
that's like not funny
if you get offended by a joke you being
offended a phony your bad a my auntie
adds guys ever funny you know now that's
it is like vote bones a scam voting is a
scam so you feel like you're involved
that's the scam of voting my anti ads
guy okay
yeah being offended is not funny what do
I think about quantum computing no I
think P equals B Q P so these times it
know if the channel gets big there's no
more channel wall for tarian I like it I
like it yes so this is a complexity
class of look good thingies quantum
computers can solve
I think it's equal to P I think people
are gonna be sorely disappointed ok so
let's see if we can get these things to
build on Mac don't think it's a scam I
think it just can't do the things people
will think it can do um I think like D
waves a scam
intelligence augmentation is a scam I
don't know about that
okay so let's see if we can get
something synthesized and building
so what's this board called I don't ever
remember it's been a long time love is
king I like that that Kanye West shit
you know we all doesn't need love that's
even download a sample project
Wow this sounds hard
I am Spanish this chat is I think this
was like the poker table that's true you
know cuz became a people colluding at
the poker table and other languages
that's a rule in Vegas is the rule in
the chat
I don't think do I think hard work beats
talent I've mean that sounds like a
clickbait headline hard work beats
talent and then you have the kind of
people who were like good cuz I don't
think of myself talented but I know I
could start working hard tomorrow do I
like sports yeah not really
oh my god oh my god the intellectual
dark web you know it's funny it's funny
you can watch it well I mean everyone's
seen those videos right but what if you
don't have talent while coding a
predicting sports model we got the
Xilinx is working whoo
I don't know what is hentai only
pornographic forms illegal here this is
rapidly industrializing the nation
number seven
fun fact I believe porn is also illegal
in Singapore but the laws are not
enforced prostitution on the other hands
is legal in Singapore but pimping is not
I know I'm not in China I told you I'm
not in China China is rapidly
industrializing nation number one and
I'm in rapidly industrializing nations
number seven now they don't have treaty
I guess this shit water oh great
type of source who treated pipe water
supply oh I should have done that with
y'all yes I believe porn is legal in
South Korea but the websites are blocked
like prostitution is illegal in Malaysia
I like to know the loss of countries cuz
I don't want to violate them like I said
I'm a guest I'm a guest and I really I
try my best to uh to behave you can help
break any of the loss so really I
respect them for having me as a guest as
opposed to America where I was born and
I've right so let's ride and do whatever
I want
to me
I would Thailand is in a similar
category to these yet I hear some
Malaysia's I hear some Indonesia's
here's Vietnam save some Cambodia's in
there I don't know anyone who's actually
been to Myanmar or Laos well no actually
the UH tb's of personal storage no no
well it's interesting in these countries
it's it's unclear of streaming porn as
illegal it's really just the possession
that's illegal
if you stream it it's less clear are you
so sure I'm cold
ok API in Thailand who knows the
drinking water you can't drink the water
here yeah it's made by 1,500 no yes I
love Thailand for girls and foods I went
to some of those I went to some of those
bars in Thailand that was uh yeah it was
like old creepy dudes there I was a
little creeped out the food's good I
like the food in Vietnam better I feel
better after I eat fought them like a
pad thai there's and a tie
every once in a while I get it there is
no sound
I'm sure there's sound we are allegedly
working so there's a CPU silence build
forget we this wise maybe it's an build
I checked it out oh yeah those may be I
know what live FPGA Linkous awesomes IPS
off not these
could be Cambodia Cambodia is definitely
around these sort of rapidly
industrialized nations could be Bangkok
do not work for terrorist organizations
it worked for North Korea long before I
would prizes North Korea has the
potential to do it for the walls Isis I
don't I just don't see it
I know if curries funny when you look at
it from an external perspective than
like the internal perspective I don't
know I mean maybe it's truly horrible to
live there I've never been
haven't really banned a lot of people
most people just get timeouts the Kim
Jong Korea yeah they have potential they
should look imagine you're Kim generally
right
imagine you're kim janghoon and your dad
died your brother got banned from being
Supreme Leader because he took I believe
his daughter to Disneyland Paris so he
couldn't be Supreme Leader so now you're
Kim Jung go now let's say you kind of
see what's going on here let's say
you're kind of like wow you know I've
been to South Korea I don't know if he's
actually been to South Korea but but
he's been he's been outside of North
Korea and he's seen the rest of the
world and he's like wow this place is
really really nice
you know there's there's beautiful
shopping malls everywhere and you know
there's no shopping malls in North Korea
at least as far as I know I mean they
could be lying to us but yeah Kim
jong-eun and you want to liberalize and
open up the borders of North Korea even
though your supreme leader you can't
just say that cuz the military guys that
have your heads so how do you do it all
I'm saying is if in ten years kim
jongmin manages to and shut down the
nuclear program open the borders of
North Korea you know get all the people
that the foreign aid they need I think
he deserves a Nobel Peace Prize I could
see a world in which kim jong hoon wins
a Nobel Peace Prize ten years there's
putting that out there I can't see any
world in which Isis ends positively
I don't know why Trump does anything you
can ask Trump you hate your job I'm
sorry I can see it I could see it he'll
be he effectively you don't say this all
those people yet yes ten years I could
be way wrong I could be way wrong but
Kim jong-un if you ever see this video
do the right thing man
the world will forgive you and you'll
live a great you'll live a great life
okay so Python HDL well this stuff I was
looking at yeah my HDL it's not the OSIS
guy maybe it is the OSIS guy
oh don't work for Google I see an actual
chance of monarchy returning to the
world um
democracy has some issues um no I want
to find okay I can't I can't find what
I'm looking for you wanna you can apply
for how may I begin he was alive during
water I don't know I think it might have
been I thought I'd downloaded this stuff
I thought I at least remember it but I
guess I always think I'm gonna remember
stuff and then I don't we have 2018 oh I
see
you guys have a king and Canada I
haven't heard I heard you guys look out
legal we congratulations
welcome to our future a monarchy is
great if you have a good king then the
only problem with monarchy in
dictatorships is with an axe guy yes
democracy's pretty good at solving the
who's the next guy problem take
marijuana you know I was new 13-inch
okay not I'm not working very fast I'm
kind of kind of lagging tonight the
shit-talking
a long day I'm kind of sick so much
excuse isn't terrible it's the guy doing
is it this guy
so these are the open-source
oh is it Cindy flow no those the people
trying yeah a project x-ray okay so
there's that
lots of risks oh here we go
FPGA tools only supports but I think
that's exactly what I have
is that the one I have
think it is
multiculturalism is seriously killing me
how so
college age how so tell me about how
multiculturalism is killing you what is
it was shitty claim what is
multiculturalism even mean and I feel
like all these things like you know like
diversity right no one a problem with
diversity until a bunch of assholes
started screaming it at the top of their
lungs everywhere
same thing with collaboration nobody had
a problem with collaboration like I grew
collaborating why don't you come to our
Meetup or will this cost collaboration
while we collaborate and jerk each other
off while collaborating I mean like
hiring for diversity without skill isn't
good this is this is 2014 political
commentary this is a 2018 I think this
is the future
okay new rule politics is banned but
meta politics is allowed only for
tonight I stopped watching it after a
bet is this
my HDL I found like a whole thing it was
a whole like FPGA Linux build
environment
no tears
Wow that's a lot of stuff oh yeah yeah
it says this is this light axe yeah this
stuff let's check this out I'm not
really sure what this is but it's using
okay it's using me Jen me Jen is what I
was thinking about - a python toolbox
for building complex digital hardware so
if there's been any yeah
yeah look at this stuff well if nobody's
CPUs are so these are people who already
have done like a lot of from the
transistor to the web browser we're just
we're just looking at it for inspiration
so bulking for those of you just joining
this dream yeah from the trance the
Taylor Swift is a new song now I can't
listen to that I don't get me so much
copyright flags
I heard Taylor Swift commented on
politics and I became much less
interested I thinking no js' in general
javascript sucks so fast though it's
true ugly language ugliest thing about
javascript is it's numbers to all
floating-point numbers
for pi
micro Python one on FPGAs good this
stuff
I think Python 2 is better as well but
except though that's not really where
the world's going this is never gonna
work
TBD Doc's great no Doc's plan expel
environment gay
supports a large number of FPGA boys but
not all boards can be used for all
projects
my board yes or no not my boy
because this is my board here so it
doesn't look like a lot of stuff as
support they have yes in question mark
okay
[Music]
why tech setup an it install
I heard of these cores before
Oh Vera laters cool it's like a compiler
for Vera log
as you in a lot of hard drive
damn some time whoa whoa guys tabs are
fucking stupid it's not politics
tabs are just stupid it's not even a
real fight everyone who believes the
tabs are better in spaces is a troll I
should be treated accordingly what
she'll check
not ever use us
ah
okay we did that step okay
I think I have to do that is already up
to date okay go to boards target and
execute the target you want to build but
you know what here's the thing about
boards and tabs we went there's no
boards with boards
did you install that as my global Python
just a link
there's no boards targets how do they
not
no we're trying to get around using HDL
they write their Corazon like Python
it's like light do you Ram
crazy
oh my god is this cloning this is
cloning
[Music]
there's still no boards there's still no
boards into the light x-lite XO here we
go boards targets mini spartan six maybe
allows us to mine
[Music]
no module named light X no module named
media ah no module named let X can't
open the file unusable garbage
[Music]
all right we're over insulting each
other about tabs and spaces no no
oh that's just running things inside the
Xilinx container I see
rebuild flappy ai
it's gonna work
all right well what if you can connect
to X server
what if the odds that's gonna work
didn't work
because I need to look forward x11
unix's or something
didn't work oh this is a rabbit hole
um no the Python three people I don't
know what you do now the Python three
was a typical example of people just
kind of being too stubborn to admit when
they were wrong like they made a mistake
and instead of saying you know what guys
like we messed up we can we can fix this
we can we can reconcile it before Python
three grew out of control they're like
no parentheses and Unicode strings are
the one true way and fuck anybody who
says otherwise and then we got Python to
endure even like nobody won the world's
eventually gonna move to Python three
but like was really was ten years of war
the parentheses are annoying and print
the Unicode strings were like it's just
gonna be able so much better having to
buddy you in front of the string was not
the end of the world just as having to
put a be in front of the end of the
strings not the end of the world either
but you know
the language was good the way it was
they didn't have to change it the
ultimate fuck you would be if they came
out with Python 4 and it was Python 2
compatible and then refused to support
Python 3 like he was just telling you
all so why don't we say we're going to
do in there from the transistor we're
going to make something blink link
must have 13 parentheses
okay well this looks kind of fun
okay we have a very log file let's see
if we can synthesize it by hand
you know about part-time but okay so
what does synthesis sin this HDL
takes in dot V files
not each prep sex this is useless
these are all the Xilinx command lines
mapping HDL entry and synthesis
xst
here we go great oh it has a it has a
friendly on my copies i links use a
local bin so if I type stylings here
okay I can just hear use deep I can just
read the friendly 100 page manual for
Xilinx xst user guide
[Music]
great it just has 27 million things so
this is the Xilinx tool chain I'm
writing is my hand to understand like
what the actual tool chain is
synthesized bearlock just emphasize
right yes
right down where I copied this front as
well that first thing might be like a
director
don't need to get those things those
things are kind of starting to see I
start with basic alto script filename
contains a set of valid xst commands no
options are specified
maybe broski with the docker
no way you know what I should be able to
do is always bash is kind of nice I
loved are you guys who ever told you how
much I love docker
no the malls closed this 10 o'clock
so he probably uses his own
she build the
dal-su I'll do it I'll do it
oh they got Domino's here
mmm-hmm Oh closes at 11:00
Thomas closes at eleven of Malaysia
sorry rapidly industrializing country
number seven
yeah they have like weird dominoes in
some place he's also like Pizza Hut they
also had pizza Hudson rapidly
industrializing nation number nine
they were definitely like a few behind
this one that that country was crazy man
and then I went to Singapore and
everything was like America they kept no
drugs
arch a Spartan sex missing arch family
oh great
Ruby sucks
so here we go okay baby reading the
Xilinx user guide as is the right idea
well I thought it was overly complicated
Oh access to user guide
this is just telling me about like the
Vera Log
somebody somewhere has to done this with
a make file here we go
IFS
undefined command feral log alvera log
work
oh god prize sir
undefined command barrel it was on a
command we learned
P
worrying about whether weed has a
negative effect on the brain has a
negative effect on the brain
I would sometimes really do don't lose
that anxiety fucking stupid jug don't do
xanax don't do ecstasy more than once a
year
don't trip more than once a year you
know caffeine's fine tax me stupid like
xanax actually makes you stupid
Oh drinking a lot too is quite bad yeah
I read some study if you like using for
a year your IQ drops eight points
I don't know though like all these
studies yeah I think it's actually worse
than drinking I don't know I wouldn't do
benzos there she drugs anyway they make
you feel stupid
and I'm not saying like you take ones
antics you're stupid I'm saying like
don't take that shit every day have you
ever had depression I don't really like
I don't view depression like that we do
you ever have depression ever been sad
yeah bro
so is weed right we weeds effects on IQ
or much less clear all these things also
could be behavioural right like all of
this dis dis damage from drugs it's not
like you have a control group that's
doing the exact same thing as the
experimental group
depression is largely a scam I have
tried like all the drugs like one small
stone I'm awesome aren't like good or
stupid
the gex is he's pretty stupid I think
tripping should be given a lot more some
groups of people is some groups of
people it gets given the kind of
reverence I think it deserves
look psychedelics like I think I think
it's a big deal I think sometimes people
take it too casually I smoke weed y'all
know I smoke weed I smoke we on stream
sometime I've never tried bath
no I smoked DMT once what's the
interesting experience so I asked for
those who don't know is DMT with a MAO
inhibitor because if you take DMT orally
ma I'll break it down before it is any
effect I will ask a mix is that I'm not
sure what I don't know what the point of
it are and I asked actually is but I
mean that it kind of scares me I don't
know if it's now it's a reversible one I
think they use so when you go to MAO
inhibitors there is reversible and
irreversible I know a lot of weird shit
about drugs
now I never watched mr. robot
come in - verilock what
that's what this scripts doing I don't
understand
I'm gonna fuck up your brain was all
what most drugs I did I did when I was a
lot younger so I fucked up my brain was
a long time ago long for a ditch yet tea
makes you smarter thank you for
subscribing and CQ they don't make you
smarter they don't even really make you
focus more a lot of especially adderall
I think a lot of what it does is hijacks
the part of your brain that makes you
think you are productive you think coke
you can really see this you go into room
a coked-up people there they're all just
screaming and think they have very
interesting things to say and you're
sober you're like looking at it real
like wow sure hope I never look like
that um enjoyable but I don't think it
makes you smarter I'm T might t my T's a
lot better than I drink coffee these
days I probably shouldn't drink coffee I
drink tea that was a really nice thing
about Osaka Osaka
okay how do I
daffa no that's super vigil back in the
day and I got some new per vigil and the
new provincial had some weird binding
agent in and it would give me awful
headaches or there is a chance that my
relationship to modafinil just just
changed this weird feels weird like you
know you don't you have like like like
alcohol we know Piet's and nymphetamine
's and these drugs feel not weird
and there's drugs like that that feel
weird but a feels weird cell gleen you
know talk about we are drug cell gleans
weird for a zine a PE a citrus type
think if T was interesting I think we
first try
lighter fluid no there's no safe way to
use inhalants everyday what to think
about
downers drugs or hype know what that
means
sampler xst script file run
there's an a Spartan and QS part some
moral support step on there
what actually is a separate fire a while
okay I missed the subtlety there
add nicotine as a as a : organic is
interesting
no Borum probably has good stuff about
it
there's a chance nicotine's actually a
decent smart drug go about your question
is it actually is not such a bad
question to say why are there so many
drugs that make you dumber and not many
make you smarter well entropy the
entropy doesn't work that way Oh tired
not tired
what musk as it figured out
oh it's doing something oh cool we did
something we're really not working very
fast tonight specification of top name
beyond tops which required yeah if you
get a to the top
Wow I think it worked cool it
synthesized oh this is so cool alright
now we have to ignore all that shit it's
not gonna work it generates all this
garbage
valerian root
okay so that was synthesis what do we
have to do next
what's next on this high winx
command-line tools
the world doesn't make sense
you know what can I say I don't upload
them to YouTube someone else does but
yeah and I mean the world doesn't make
sense who told you it should then you
know they should teach kids that the
world's not fair
had a really engage it'll set him up for
success later in life try to teach kids
the World's Fair sass him up for failure
well friend she's like you know my
parents when I was growing up sometimes
they'd give my brother shit and they
wouldn't give me shit and I'd be like
but I want to present to and they'd be
like well you know life's not fair and
you're gonna learn that at some points
better than you learning now and she's
an incredibly well-adjusted lovely human
being what can I say that's right it's
like all right so that was synthesis now
our path services now we're gonna do
constraints maybe mapping the input to
map is an NG defiled we have one of
those no we have an NGC file unzip a
file can be placed and routed take some
map well I like that that that make file
seems pretty good
to find that again
ms:i are so loudly yeah they're all
cuddly I would only be okay MGD build
it's an ng d ng d build up speed target
part we know the target part it's a
Spartan 6w we need a project we don't
have an ng o an ng C file well we have
one of those
Oh lovely well it has on some garbage in
it great - oh map dot NGC oh we need a
PCF file I don't know not for this one
we don't
oops I'm getting confused go NGC go ng D
all it makes NGC files into an g DS all
right this is a make file
Oh do we have an N GD ho given ng D now
what's an n GT nobody knows you say
maybe it'll tell me ng D build turns
netlist into made of generic database oh
I know what that is
there's only make fire useful see why I
like having multiple monitors we don't
have to keep reco going the same shit
like put this on a monitor over there
but I only have one monitor for you - oh
jeez map P spawn sex W we have an N GD
file that's good news
oh well this makes an end a CD file
maybe it makes a PC f as well
incomplete targets part specification no
device has been specified for
architecture Spartan sixth okay
valid architectures that's an ark at all
no device has been specified for
architecture aspire than sex
good enough for the other ones
workspaces what is that
I mean like is the thing guys built into
Mac OSX
I'm swiping with five fingers
I kind of remember this is this what you
mean
describe what I'm doing
no you can watch and you can try to
figure it out I don't know what I'm
doing maybe you do
swipe up with four fingers I hate that
you know part number oh okay a complete
part number consists of the following so
now here's why type it's the only one
that's supported by that opening chorus
thing so we can just come and pitch from
there right
I'd open core as well as it called PGH
holes yes that can work
see I don't know if that's an out file
or an in file PCF I wanted FWD won't
even know that work no package has been
specified
oh here we go
architecture only device - package what
packages
it's kind of like yeah yeah it's like
project Icestorm yeah sure yeah
something like that you know so so right
it's whatever you say it is whoo it does
something I'm sure I'm sure it's very
useful for some people somewhere to do
something that's the package CSG what's
a CSG package ship scale VG I never
heard of it
Oh licensing error knee license
oh that knows more bullshit than I need
to have to get ignore a who got a
license for that man hey
temple OS you don't work on that for
years ten years pro religious devotion
Dow respect no respect temple or less oh
okay so it said some bullshit about how
to get the license I don't know guys I'm
kind of tired movie this bedtime you're
trying to catch tomorrow train to poor
there's room for real like Rome Korea
Terry Pepe hands that would be status
I'm having the temple Alaska it was cool
no I only take train oh yeah Eastern and
oriental express I was looking this
stuff up but it's crazy expensive this
is a lot more oh yeah look at how much
ring get to that as all that's so cheap
anyone can afford that okay well now we
know what train options I have buy this
train
all right so we're gonna leave the I see
I think that's all the actual
programming rota tonight if you came
here for the programming that's over if
you came here to try to watch me get a
ticket to the next destination in
Malaysia we are in Malaysia rapidly
developing country number seven only a
ticket
don't take the family on an adventure I
look at that branding look at the
branding I love that what's the brand
for Amtrak
I wish this website worked
[Laughter]
to give that America we're gonna be
crushed
oh I gotta go to pull out
pull out pull out go to pull out but I
can't provide destination in focus it
doesn't load
refresh
all right I'm gonna buy this train
ticket on my own business embarrassing
embarrassing ly bad at this
so where did what did we do tonight well
we got the Xilinx stuff installed in the
docker by largely following instructions
we learned about some things that we're
gonna have to do we're gonna have to get
the license file we'll do that next time
and then once we get something compiling
we'll be able to actually download it
using my download script little brusky
here all right thank you for joining
tonight the twitch stream will try to be
streaming a bit more assuming we're in
hotels that have upstream bandwidth
thank you for joining you know I really
appreciate all of the support everybody
who subscribes to me you know these
these train tickets are not cheap
just this train ticket is gonna cost me
between 19 and 35 ringgit so 35
malaysian ringgit 2 USD that's gonna
cost me eight dollars and 37 cents
um so if you guys could subscribe so i
could have $8.37 so i could afford to
train to get out of Johor Bahru i would
really appreciate it and please please
give me money and subscribe we're back
to that twitch was twitch was not fun
when we weren't shilling it was only fun
when we shell and talk about drugs and
don't talk about politics the whole I'm
never getting back to the US I can't
afford it I got I played by stream
better take off if I want to be able to
ever get back to the US now where we're
riding the we're riding the Sun twitch a
sawfish this was fun no we're riding the
slow train too
Danny dollars hey Tyler come on give me
money guys give me money I need money
ease I need I need money please give me
money so I can afford my train ticket
but but it's not just this train I have
to take another train tow this trains
gonna cost me another twelve to fifteen
ringgit and what if I want to premiere
see you let's see what a premiere seat
is just look nice let's say well this
one doesn't even give me price choice
well that's just a guess
ice Malaysia language people speak
English I likes English you know speaks
English laughs want to have great words
and it's English like kiasu you know jet
kiasu Singaporean say oh yeah no I was
learning all about
she's upon telling us here I can't
depend on life see this English to a
pencil guys have deal Singlish is so
cool but it's also kind of like new
speed so I don't really know how I feel
about that
these are poor Thomas here you know this
is this year or even know
yeah
I don't know I'm over hacking we were
just casually playing with that PGI
stuff tonight alright thank you for
watching I'll try a stream or I probably
won't my webcams low-quality goodbye